So today you can check out my episode of Surrounded.
Black culture is toxic.
And let's not, let's get on the fact that there's no fathers in the black house.
Let's get, let's get, let's talk about that.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I'm Black Radical surrounded by 20 black conservatives on YouTube for free.
Or you can support my work and pay $5 to subscribe to my Patreon,
where you'll get all the goods of Patreon in addition to at 7 p.m. Eastern tonight
a watch with me of my episode of Surrounded.
I have not seen the episode.
I've seen clips.
The clips are a part of a one hour and 40 minute episode because there's an edit.
There's going to be parts that they leave out.
So I will be filling you in with that tea.
I will also be providing you with my additional insights that I didn't get to say on screen.
And I'll also be answering questions.
So the watch with me is an interactive experience of my episode of Surrounded,
which is one black radical versus 20 black conservatives.
We all deserve a right to exist.
And I shouldn't have to earn my right to exist.
And that is what capitalism does.
What makes you think that you have to earn it?
That's what I'm saying.
I don't feel that way.
You do have to earn it.
You do.
Yes, you do.
That is why we are criminalizing the poor.
And I hope that you'll join me because I will absolutely appreciate the community support.
And I know that there's been a lot of people who have been voicing their desire to not support Jubilee.
They apparently don't like, you know, the content that Jubilee puts out, etc.
I have no qualms about that.
If you still want to support me, though, then you can get two birds with one stone.
But no, we don't like that phrase.
You can feed two birds with one stone.
Um, by subscribing to patreon.com backslash America Feels.
And, uh, I know a lot of you all said that this episode might give you anxiety.
Well, here's a way to share with each other that anxiety.
Therefore, you don't have to shoulder it yourself.
I do think, however, it is an important episode to watch.
And I want you all to understand, you know, why I chose to do this.
And I think it's best shared in real time.
So I'll see you there at 7 p.m. Eastern.
Patreon.com backslash Amanda Seals for one black radical surrounded by 20 black conservatives.
Ooh, I knew I was going to be surrounded by ignorance.
But damn, let's go.
Let's go.